Chris Adkins

http://www.github.com/CNAtion96 | http://www.chrisnadkins.com

I am a Front-end Developer with a passion for learning. I started learning to program five years ago as a hobby and it has grown into the passion that I have today. I may be new to the field, but I have the drive to learn and develop my skills as a developer.

50 Apple Drive Independence, KY 41051 (304) 410-2849 adkins.chris1996@gmail.com

TECH SKILLS

React JS

Angular JS

Git

Github

Javascript

HTML5

CSS3

jQuery

Ajax

Sass

Node.js

MongoDB

Express JS

Bootstrap

EDUCATION

The Iron Yard, Cincinnati, OH

FEBRUARY 2017 - MAY 2017

A twelve week bootcamp where I studied and was certified in Front-end Development.

Marshall University, Huntington, WV

AUGUST 2014 - MAY 2016

I spent two years at Marshall studying Computer Science.

EXPERIENCE

FedEx Ground, Florence, Ky — Package Handler

July 2017 - Present

I was responsible for handling customer packages and loading them without damaging them.

Amazon, Hebron, Ky — Fulfillment Associate

AUGUST 2016 - FEBRUARY 2017

I was responsible for sorting and wrapping packages for shipment.

Walmart, Barboursville, WV — Cashier

JULY 2016 - AUGUST 2016

I was responsible for processing transactions and helping customers whenever I could whether or not it was in my department.

Subway, Barboursville, WV — Sandwich Artist

APRIL 2016 - JULY 2016

I was responsible for making sandwiches, processing transactions, and keeping inventory.